[{"answer": "No I haven't seen it yet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm goin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nobody died. Jack I want you to do me a big favor.  In my garage there are a couple of boxes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm gonna explain what boxes", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Ok, see you later", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What show", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh hi my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "My idiot son could open that garage door", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Just do it first thing tomorrow. I need it.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ya that was some list", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " The black and white", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's righ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You're right he's ripping me of", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Ya so have ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't think it's fair", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No no, I found the place, I set the whole thing up, I'm doing all the leg work", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, there's leg work", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes, he's insane, that's what I think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know, I don't know what to do.  Oh god.... so how was the movie", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I don't know, I don't know what to do.  Oh god.... so how was the movie", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Ya what do you mean from what you saw", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Uh from what I saw it was pretty good", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well I um I didn't ah actually get to see the whole movie", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yea why not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " You were making, out during my friend's List", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " We're both living with our parents", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No I don't think so. I saw my friend as I was leaving but see me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We have to make the flight, we're with a charter group. If we don't the trip is off", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Some place else? What about that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You know, I was thinking today. I never liked those Seinfelds anyway, he's an idiot all together.  Ah there's my friend.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Hell", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What happens to charter tickets when you don't use em", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes I suppose they are", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I'm the father", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "He said I was dead", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Ok.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Bye.", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "my friend? my friend are you ok", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You did enough", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Pair of bear claws please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Hello my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Say, I happened to catch you coming out of my friend's List the other night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Raincoats-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes I was", "qsentId": 44}]